Chad Hann

3523 Tree Top Lane. Pittsburgh, PA 19108 chadhann@exampie.com (123) 456-7891

Hard-working management consultant who is an IT expert and former systems analyst with an MBA in Business

Technology Management from Carnegie Mellon University. Recognized for speed, quality, and reliability for work at

both Mckinseyand Highmark.

Education

Master of Business
Administration
Carnegie Mellon University, Pittsburgh,
PA. January 2016 ■ May 2018

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology University Of Missouri Columbia, MO, January 2012 - May 2016

Key Skills

- Problem Solving
- Project Management
- Microsoft Excel
- Relationship Building
- Organization
- Information Technology
- ♦ HTML,Java, PHP

Professional Experience

Management Consultant-Technology

McKinsey & Company, Pittsburg, PA | December 2020 - Present

- Design strategies for companies Looking to break into, or stay competitive in, the global electronic economy.
- Named "Business Technology Management Consultant of the Year" at McKinsey's Pittsburgh Branch in 2020 for outstanding and consistent project outcomes.
- Identify and assess complex business and technology risks, create performance indicators, and plan for transitions to new processes.
- Highly requested by clients for work on information technology solutions to common business problems.

IT Systems Analyst

Highmark, Inc., Pittsburgh, PA | September 2018 - November 2020

- Avoided system failure and reduced downtime by evaluating, monitoring, and correcting system network problems.
- Remained in the top three out of 85 company analysts for speed in resolving issues.
- Designed, built, and maintained databases for a variety of internal products.
- Collaborated with the scrum team to ascertain and suggest designs or solutions for projects.